nimu or nimu's new dog has
nimu o el nuevo perro de nimu le ha
paid nimu's old dog money,
pagado al antiguo perro de nimu dinero o
so what a coincidence that suddenly
sea Qué casualidad que de repente sale
something so strong about nimu comes out and what a
una cosa tan fuerte de nimu y Qué
coincidence that a few hours later
casualidad que a las pocas horas sale
keno comes out to defend nimu with erab and
keno a defender a nimu con erab y de
suddenly that tweet has 40,000 likes it doesn't
repente ese tweet tiene 40.000 likes no
seem like ingredients that coincide much he makes
parece ingredientes que coinciden mucho
you pretend on social networks that it
te ponga a fingir en redes sociales que
was all a lie a troll exactly
era todo mentira un troleo exactamente
what If in fact he himself is so
de qué Si de hecho él mismo es tan
pathetic that he starts to confirm that the
patético que se pone a confirmar que la
information is true as you can see it is
información es cierta como podéis ver es
true there is no troll he has posted a
verdad no hay ningún troleo él ha puesto
tweet before saying that it was a troll
tweet antes de decir que era un troleo
of course this one has come to him and they have
claro este le han venido y le han
put him in Manteca but it's not
juntado en Manteca pero es que no es
just that the guy is so but so so so big
solo eso el tipo es tan pero tan tan tan
mouth that the piece of clown goes and
bocazas que el pedazo de payaso va y me
tells me XD here wins whoever pays more this is
dice XD aquí gana quien paga más esto es
very funny eh but really what I
muy divertido eh pero de verdad yo lo
understand from here is that nimu or
que entiendo de aquí es que nimu o el
nimu's new dog paid money to
nuevo perro de nimu le pagó dinero al
nimu's old dog to start pretending
antiguo perro de nimu para que se ponga
on social networks that everything was
a fingir en redes sociales que todo era
false garo exactly
falso garo exactamente